firstcommunity.com 2011-05-02

# First Community Credit Union - Privacy Policy

|  | 

PERSONAL BANKING

---|---  
  
**FOR YOUR SAFETY:** Fraudulent calls and text messages may be sent to members asking for personal and account information. First Community Credit Union would never call members asking for this type of information. Please beware and **DO NOT** give out any information to these callers. Always call First Community at **636-728-3333 or 1-800-767-8880** if you have any concerns of this nature.

* * *

**Introduction**  
First Community Credit Union recognizes and respects how important personal privacy is to you. Because of our interest in protecting your privacy, we continually examine the operating practices and procedures of our organization. First Community Credit Union has adopted the following privacy policy, continuing in our commitment to provide quality service to you, our valued member.

**Recognition of Our Member's Expectation of Privacy**  
First Community Credit Union recognizes that our members expect and deserve privacy and security for their personal and financial matters. We understand the need to safeguard the sensitive information that our members have entrusted to us. We maintain standards and procedures designed to protect the misuse of this information.

**Our Collection, Use and Retention of Member Information**  
We collect, use and retain information about our members only where we reasonably believe it would be useful in administering our business, by providing products and services, and other opportunities to our members. We collect and retain information only for specific business purposes and will tell you why we are collecting and retaining it upon your request. You may contact the credit union at the address and phone number shown below. We use information to protect and administer our members' records, accounts, and funds; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help design or improve our products and services; to understand the financial needs to appropriately market our services and provide quality products and outstanding service. And this information will not be reused. Although we may disclose account information to our vendors that assist the Credit Union in completing transactions, we do not share any of our information with any business partners for their sole marketing purposes.

**Our Maintenance of Accurate Information**  
We have implemented procedures to help assure that our members' financial information is accurate, current, and complete in accordance with commercial standards. While some procedures are required by federal or state law, we also have procedures for responding to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner, and to update information and remove old information. Members should notify us immediately if they receive information regarding their relationship with the credit union that they believe to be inaccurate. You may contact the credit union at the address and phone number shown below.

**Limiting Employee Access to Information**  
We have procedures and security levels in place that limit employee access to personally identifiable information to those with a business reason to know such information. We educate our employees on the importance of confidentiality and member privacy.

**Protection of Information**  
We maintain security standards and procedures to help prevent unauthorized access to confidential member information. We update and test our technology to improve the protection of our member information and to assure the integrity of our information.

**Restrictions on the Disclosures of Account Information**  
First Community Credit Union shares information regarding members only in accordance with strict confidentiality policies and with applicable law. Third parties are not given access to account access numbers (such as PIN numbers) or similar access numbers for marketing purposes. We do not reveal specific information about our members' accounts or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated parties for their independent use, unless (1) our member has requested it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by our member; (3) the information is provided to a reputable credit bureau or similar information reporting agency; or (4) disclosure is lawfully permitted or required. The above applies both to current members, and to those persons who are no longer members of the Credit Union.

**Maintaining Member Privacy in Business Relationships with Outside Third Parties**  
At times it is necessary to provide personally identifiable information about our members to a third party, such as a vendor that we hire to prepare your account statements. All third-party vendors agree to safeguard our confidential member information, are not permitted to reuse information for unauthorized purposes, and must abide by applicable law.

**Online Personal Information**  
This section describes the circumstances under which we may receive personal information online.

First Community Credit Union is committed to the highest level of security and privacy regarding the collection and use of our online account access (using Expressnet) members' personal information, as well as that of all visitors to our web site. Personal information may be collected through the submission of account applications, online account access transactions, or through the use of online financial tools such as interactive calculators. Visitors may also voluntarily provide us with personal information via e-mail, drawing registrations, web surveys, online registration, guestbook or contact forms. This information is handled internally by our staff to process the visitor's request. First Community Credit Union does use standard Web tracking software to collect nonidentifying information about our visitors, such as:

      Date and time our site was accessed
      City, state and country
      Web browser used
      IP address (a numeric address given to
      servers connected to the internet)

The credit union uses this information to create summary statistics and to determine the level of interest in our web site.

**Website Links**  
The internet contains many useful resources, and First Community Credit Union contains links to other websites. First Community Credit Union is not responsible for the privacy practices, content or availability of the linked websites. We also encourage users to read the privacy statement of all linked websites to become acquainted with their specific privacy practices.

**Protecting Children**  
First Community Credit Union recognizes that protecting children's identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility rests with both the online industry and the parents. The Credit Union does not collect any personal information on children through its website, but does offer online links through the website to various child-oriented sites. Please be advised that any site collecting information from children under the age of 13 must conform to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA).

**Online Banking Pages**  
To ensure your privacy and financial security, we require that you enter a password before you may logon to our online account access service. We have also implemented "Enhanced log-in Security" which strengthens security at login by providing an additional end user authentication factor beyond the user name and password. Account access pages are encrypted using "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL).

To ensure valid navigation access from your computer to our host servers we employ the use of "Cookies". Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. These also allow us to know if you have visited the site before. Cookies are also used for security purposes in conjunction with "enhanced log-in security" to recognize your computer. Our Cookies do not contain any information that would identify you personally. You can generally configure your web browser to block cookies, but doing so may restrict your access to any secured site, including ours.

**Your E-Mail Privacy**  
First Community Credit Union's web site does not require you to disclose any personal identifying information. If, however, you choose to contact us via e-mail, please keep in mind that your e-mail address, and any other information your e-mail header shows about you, such as your name or organization, will be revealed to us in the e-mail. We pledge, however, that when you communicate with us via e-mail, we will use your e-mail information only for the specific purpose of responding to your comments or questions. Your e-mail address will not be sold nor will it be shared with others outside the credit union unless we are compelled to do so by law.

**How You Can Help Protect Your Information**  
In addition, to Credit Union efforts to protect your privacy, you can follow these steps to protect yourself: 

  * Protect account and card numbers, personal identification numbers, and passwords. Keep items with personal information in a safe place.
  * Use caution when disclosing your account numbers and social security numbers to other people.
  * Keep your information with us current. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know. It is important that we have current information on how to reach you.

**Disclosing Our Privacy Commitment to Our Members**  
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy. This policy will be changed when required by law or regulation. Members will be notified of this policy at least annually when they join the Credit Union, unless a more frequent period is required by law or circumstances. If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, you may write or phone us at:

| 

      First Community Credit Union
      PO Box 1030
      Chesterfield, MO 63006
      (636) 537-4400
      Contact: Compliance Officer

|  Annual Privacy Notice  
---|---  
  
**rev. 10/2007**
